<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Economics on The Little Dataset</title>
    <link>/tags/economics/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Economics on The Little Dataset</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 23 Jul 2018 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/tags/economics/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Testing for Local Continuity in Racial Animus</title>
      <link>/2018/07/23/testing-for-local-continuity-in-racial-animus/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Jul 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2018/07/23/testing-for-local-continuity-in-racial-animus/</guid>
      <description>This past spring I was tasked with writing a final paper for my Comparative Historical Economic Development course. In brainstorming, I started a casual fling with one idea that quickly escalated and led to long spring break dates at the library (collecting data, making maps). In a meeting with my professor back at Harvard, I realized that I had been consumed in the honeymoon phase of an idea. Taking off my rose-colored glasses, it became clear I had to end the tryst so I could focus on more promising paths to a paper&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Social Networks and the Endurance of Economic Injury</title>
      <link>/2018/01/29/social-networks-and-the-endurance-of-economic-injury/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Jan 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2018/01/29/social-networks-and-the-endurance-of-economic-injury/</guid>
      <description>Killing Two Birds with One Paper My last fall semester exam was for Social Economics class. Reading through packets of model summaries, I set out to determine which model &amp;ndash; besides the obviously lovable Coate and Loury (1993) &amp;ndash; I would most like to understand, remember, and explain. That is, I picked a paper to write about here&amp;hellip; which I could also use in my intellectual battle with those pesky blue books.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>On Ego and Sharing Ideas</title>
      <link>/2017/10/12/on-ego-and-sharing-ideas/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Oct 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2017/10/12/on-ego-and-sharing-ideas/</guid>
      <description>A behavioral Nobel means a behavioral blog post In honor of Richard Thaler&amp;rsquo;s recent Nobel prize win, I give you a post on a behavioral economics topic! Welcome to round 2 of A G2 Talks Models. Today&amp;rsquo;s topic: ego utility and the decision to speak up in class à la Koszegi 2006, an approach to belief-based utility adapted from Psychology and Economics lecture.
An admission of ego I have a confession to make.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>You Think, Therefore I Am</title>
      <link>/2017/09/07/you-think-there-i-am/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Sep 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2017/09/07/you-think-there-i-am/</guid>
      <description>Intro Hello world, I am now a G2 in economics PhD-land. This means I have moved up in the academic hierarchy; I now reign over my very own cube, and I am taking classes in my fields of interest. For me that means: Social Economics, Behavioral Economics, and Market Design. That also means I am coming across a lot of models, concepts, results that I want to tell you (whoever you are!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Bellman Equation About Nothing</title>
      <link>/2017/03/21/a-bellman-equation-about-nothing/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Mar 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2017/03/21/a-bellman-equation-about-nothing/</guid>
      <description>Cold Open A few years ago I came across a short paper that I desperately wanted to understand. The magnificent title was &amp;ldquo;An Option Value Problem from Seinfeld&amp;rdquo; and the author, Professor Avinash Dixit (of Dixit-Stiglitz model fame), therein discussed methods of solving for &amp;ldquo;sponge-worthiness.&amp;rdquo; I don&amp;rsquo;t think I need to explain why I was immediately drawn to an academic article that focuses on Elaine Benes, but for those of you who didn&amp;rsquo;t learn about the realities of birth control from this episode of 1990&amp;rsquo;s television, allow me to briefly explain the relevant Seinfeld-ism.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Anxious Optimization</title>
      <link>/2016/10/26/anxious-optimization/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2016/10/26/anxious-optimization/</guid>
      <description>On the morning of my dynamic programming midterm, I tried to calm myself by recalling the golden rules of grad school that have been passed down through the generations1:
 grades don&amp;rsquo;t matter&amp;hellip; nothing matters.
 However, I quickly realized that by adopting this perspective I was simply subbing out test anxiety for existential anxiety. And, come to think of it, the latter didn&amp;rsquo;t seem to be helpful, while the former could actually aid in my short-term goals &amp;ndash; namely, jotting down lots of equations into a collection of small blue booklets.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Alex&#39;s Adventures in Academia-land</title>
      <link>/2016/05/08/alex-s-adventures-in-academia-land/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 May 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2016/05/08/alex-s-adventures-in-academia-land/</guid>
      <description>Intro While I usually use this blog to work on casual pet projects, I wanted to take an opportunity to use the medium to discuss academic research. Writing is an instinctive mechanism for me to process my thoughts on a topic, but it is one that I use sparingly to discuss the meta-narrative of my own decisions and behavior. The impetus for this self-reflection is the following exciting news: I’ll be pursuing my PhD in economics at Harvard starting this fall!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How I Learned to Stop Worrying and Love Economics</title>
      <link>/2016/03/16/how-i-learned-to-stop-worrying-and-love-economics/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Mar 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2016/03/16/how-i-learned-to-stop-worrying-and-love-economics/</guid>
      <description>Intro Many months ago, in October, the Economics Nobel prize was awarded to Angus Deaton. Beyond experiencing sheer joy at having beaten my friend Mike at predicting the winner, I also was overwhelmed by the routine, yearly backlash against the discipline in the form of articles shared widely across any and all social networks. Of particular interest to me this year was the Guardian&amp;rsquo;s piece &amp;ldquo;Don’t let the Nobel prize fool you.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>This Post is Brought to You by the National Science Foundation</title>
      <link>/2015/12/31/this-post-is-brought-to-you-by-the-national-science-foundation/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Dec 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2015/12/31/this-post-is-brought-to-you-by-the-national-science-foundation/</guid>
      <description>Intro I have officially finished applying for my PhD. While the application process included many of the same elements that I had previously encountered as a fresh-faced1 17-year-old (think standardized testing without the #2 pencils and lots more button clicking), I am no longer applying as a (relatively) blank slate&amp;ndash;a future liberal arts student who will float and skip between disciplines until being neatly slotted into a major. Instead, we PhD applicants have already zeroed in on a particular area of study&amp;ndash;in my case, economics.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>