<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Line charts on The Little Dataset</title>
    <link>/categories/line-charts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Line charts on The Little Dataset</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 14 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/categories/line-charts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Dynamics of Pretrial Jail Populations</title>
      <link>/2019/01/14/dynamics-of-pretrial-jail-populations/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2019/01/14/dynamics-of-pretrial-jail-populations/</guid>
      <description>A Daily Census of Pretrial Inmates I&amp;rsquo;ve spent a good amount of time this fall learning about pretrial detention and bail setting practices across the country. While much of the empirical research I&amp;rsquo;ve encountered on pretrial detention uses either aggregated1 or restricted access data, it turns out that there is a granular pretrial detention dataset that frollicks freely on the internet. As of 7/1/16, Connecticut has published &amp;ldquo;a daily census of every inmate held in jail while awaiting trial.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Text Me Back</title>
      <link>/2018/04/27/text-me-back-a-year-of-ldr-communication/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2018/04/27/text-me-back-a-year-of-ldr-communication/</guid>
      <description>Motivation I spent some time in February figuring out how to download my iMessage data.1 The idea was that I could then use that data to make Jesse an R Notebook Valentine. And it worked!
  A slide from my February R-ladies talk   That Valentine was an investigation into word usage (via tf-idf) and emotional tinges in messages (via sentiment dictionaries). I treated all the messages as two aggregated blocks (one from Jesse, one from me) and was not concerned with the time dimension (when messages were sent).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>On Ego and Sharing Ideas</title>
      <link>/2017/10/12/on-ego-and-sharing-ideas/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Oct 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2017/10/12/on-ego-and-sharing-ideas/</guid>
      <description>A behavioral Nobel means a behavioral blog post In honor of Richard Thaler&amp;rsquo;s recent Nobel prize win, I give you a post on a behavioral economics topic! Welcome to round 2 of A G2 Talks Models. Today&amp;rsquo;s topic: ego utility and the decision to speak up in class à la Koszegi 2006, an approach to belief-based utility adapted from Psychology and Economics lecture.
An admission of ego I have a confession to make.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The One With All The Quantifiable Friendships, Part 2</title>
      <link>/2017/06/26/the-one-with-all-the-quantifiable-friendships-part-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jun 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2017/06/26/the-one-with-all-the-quantifiable-friendships-part-2/</guid>
      <description>Since finishing my first year of my PhD, I have been spending some quality time with my computer. Sure, the two of us had been together all throughout the academic year, but we weren&amp;rsquo;t doing much together besides pdf-viewing and type-setting. Around spring break, when I discovered you can in fact freeze your computer by having too many exams/section notes/textbooks simultaneously open, I promised my MacBook that over the summer we would try some new things together.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Bellman Equation About Nothing</title>
      <link>/2017/03/21/a-bellman-equation-about-nothing/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Mar 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2017/03/21/a-bellman-equation-about-nothing/</guid>
      <description>Cold Open A few years ago I came across a short paper that I desperately wanted to understand. The magnificent title was &amp;ldquo;An Option Value Problem from Seinfeld&amp;rdquo; and the author, Professor Avinash Dixit (of Dixit-Stiglitz model fame), therein discussed methods of solving for &amp;ldquo;sponge-worthiness.&amp;rdquo; I don&amp;rsquo;t think I need to explain why I was immediately drawn to an academic article that focuses on Elaine Benes, but for those of you who didn&amp;rsquo;t learn about the realities of birth control from this episode of 1990&amp;rsquo;s television, allow me to briefly explain the relevant Seinfeld-ism.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Go East, Young Woman</title>
      <link>/2016/07/27/go-east-young-woman/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Jul 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2016/07/27/go-east-young-woman/</guid>
      <description>We&amp;rsquo;ll always have Palo Alto1 It is 9:30pm PST on Friday evening and my seat beat is buckled. The lights are a dim purple as they always are on Virgin America flights. As if we are all headed off to a prom on the opposite side of the country together. My favorite safety video in the industry starts to play&amp;ndash;an accumulation of visuals and beats that usually gives me a giddy feeling that only Beyoncé videos have the power to provoke&amp;ndash;however, in this moment, I begin to tear up despite the image of a shimmying nun displayed in front of me.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Where My Girls At? (In The Sciences)</title>
      <link>/2016/05/24/where-my-girls-at-in-the-sciences/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 May 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2016/05/24/where-my-girls-at-in-the-sciences/</guid>
      <description>Intro In the current educational landscape, there is a constant stream of calls to improve female representation in the sciences. However, the call to action is often framed within the aforementioned nebulous realm of “the sciences”—an umbrella term that ignores the distinct environments across the scientific disciplines. To better understand the true state of women in “the sciences,” we must investigate representation at the discipline level in the context of both undergraduate and doctoral education.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>&#39;Serial&#39; and Changes of Heart</title>
      <link>/2014/12/21/serial-and-changes-of-heart/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Dec 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2014/12/21/serial-and-changes-of-heart/</guid>
      <description>Intro During this past/last week of the podcast Serial, Sarah Koenig explains (unsurprisingly) that throughout her journalistic investigation of the murder of Hae Min Lee she has changed her opinion many times about Adnan&amp;rsquo;s guilt or innocence:
 Several times, I have landed on a decision, I’ve made up my mind and stayed there, with relief and then inevitably, I learn something I didn’t know before and I’m up ended.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>