<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Science on The Little Dataset</title>
    <link>/tags/science/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Science on The Little Dataset</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 26 Jul 2017 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/tags/science/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>A Rising Tide Lifts All Podcasts</title>
      <link>/2017/07/26/a-rising-tide-lifts-all-podcasts/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Jul 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2017/07/26/a-rising-tide-lifts-all-podcasts/</guid>
      <description>A Personal History of Podcast Listening One afternoon of my junior year, I listened to a chunk of a Radiolab episode about &amp;ldquo;Sleep&amp;rdquo; as I myself heavily sank into unconsciousness. It was like guided meditation&amp;hellip; supported, in part, by the Alfred P. Sloan Foundation. Jad and Robert&amp;rsquo;s forays on Radiolab quickly became my new bedtime stories. They helped me transition from days with my nose deep in books and, more accurately, my laptop to dreams that veered away from the geographic markers of one tiny college town in a valley of the Berkshires.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Where My Girls At? (In The Sciences)</title>
      <link>/2016/05/24/where-my-girls-at-in-the-sciences/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 May 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2016/05/24/where-my-girls-at-in-the-sciences/</guid>
      <description>Intro In the current educational landscape, there is a constant stream of calls to improve female representation in the sciences. However, the call to action is often framed within the aforementioned nebulous realm of “the sciences”—an umbrella term that ignores the distinct environments across the scientific disciplines. To better understand the true state of women in “the sciences,” we must investigate representation at the discipline level in the context of both undergraduate and doctoral education.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Alex&#39;s Adventures in Academia-land</title>
      <link>/2016/05/08/alex-s-adventures-in-academia-land/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 May 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2016/05/08/alex-s-adventures-in-academia-land/</guid>
      <description>Intro While I usually use this blog to work on casual pet projects, I wanted to take an opportunity to use the medium to discuss academic research. Writing is an instinctive mechanism for me to process my thoughts on a topic, but it is one that I use sparingly to discuss the meta-narrative of my own decisions and behavior. The impetus for this self-reflection is the following exciting news: I’ll be pursuing my PhD in economics at Harvard starting this fall!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How I Learned to Stop Worrying and Love Economics</title>
      <link>/2016/03/16/how-i-learned-to-stop-worrying-and-love-economics/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Mar 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2016/03/16/how-i-learned-to-stop-worrying-and-love-economics/</guid>
      <description>Intro Many months ago, in October, the Economics Nobel prize was awarded to Angus Deaton. Beyond experiencing sheer joy at having beaten my friend Mike at predicting the winner, I also was overwhelmed by the routine, yearly backlash against the discipline in the form of articles shared widely across any and all social networks. Of particular interest to me this year was the Guardian&amp;rsquo;s piece &amp;ldquo;Don’t let the Nobel prize fool you.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>This Post is Brought to You by the National Science Foundation</title>
      <link>/2015/12/31/this-post-is-brought-to-you-by-the-national-science-foundation/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Dec 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2015/12/31/this-post-is-brought-to-you-by-the-national-science-foundation/</guid>
      <description>Intro I have officially finished applying for my PhD. While the application process included many of the same elements that I had previously encountered as a fresh-faced1 17-year-old (think standardized testing without the #2 pencils and lots more button clicking), I am no longer applying as a (relatively) blank slate&amp;ndash;a future liberal arts student who will float and skip between disciplines until being neatly slotted into a major. Instead, we PhD applicants have already zeroed in on a particular area of study&amp;ndash;in my case, economics.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>