<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Scatter plots on The Little Dataset</title>
    <link>/categories/scatter-plots/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Scatter plots on The Little Dataset</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 27 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/categories/scatter-plots/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Text Me Back</title>
      <link>/2018/04/27/text-me-back-a-year-of-ldr-communication/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2018/04/27/text-me-back-a-year-of-ldr-communication/</guid>
      <description>Motivation I spent some time in February figuring out how to download my iMessage data.1 The idea was that I could then use that data to make Jesse an R Notebook Valentine. And it worked!
  A slide from my February R-ladies talk   That Valentine was an investigation into word usage (via tf-idf) and emotional tinges in messages (via sentiment dictionaries). I treated all the messages as two aggregated blocks (one from Jesse, one from me) and was not concerned with the time dimension (when messages were sent).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Rising Tide Lifts All Podcasts</title>
      <link>/2017/07/26/a-rising-tide-lifts-all-podcasts/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Jul 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2017/07/26/a-rising-tide-lifts-all-podcasts/</guid>
      <description>A Personal History of Podcast Listening One afternoon of my junior year, I listened to a chunk of a Radiolab episode about &amp;ldquo;Sleep&amp;rdquo; as I myself heavily sank into unconsciousness. It was like guided meditation&amp;hellip; supported, in part, by the Alfred P. Sloan Foundation. Jad and Robert&amp;rsquo;s forays on Radiolab quickly became my new bedtime stories. They helped me transition from days with my nose deep in books and, more accurately, my laptop to dreams that veered away from the geographic markers of one tiny college town in a valley of the Berkshires.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Where My Girls At? (In The Sciences)</title>
      <link>/2016/05/24/where-my-girls-at-in-the-sciences/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 May 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2016/05/24/where-my-girls-at-in-the-sciences/</guid>
      <description>Intro In the current educational landscape, there is a constant stream of calls to improve female representation in the sciences. However, the call to action is often framed within the aforementioned nebulous realm of “the sciences”—an umbrella term that ignores the distinct environments across the scientific disciplines. To better understand the true state of women in “the sciences,” we must investigate representation at the discipline level in the context of both undergraduate and doctoral education.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Curious Case of The Illinois Trump Delegates</title>
      <link>/2016/03/18/the-curious-case-of-the-illinois-trump-delegates/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Mar 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2016/03/18/the-curious-case-of-the-illinois-trump-delegates/</guid>
      <description>Intro This past Wednesday, after watching Hillary Clinton slow-motion strut into the Broad City universe and realizing that this election has successfully seeped into even the most intimate of personal rituals, I planned to go to sleep without thinking any more about the current presidential race. However, somewhere in between Ilana&amp;rsquo;s final &amp;ldquo;yas queen&amp;rdquo; and hitting the pillow, I saw David Wasserman&amp;rsquo;s FiveThirtyEight article &amp;ldquo;Trump Voters’ Aversion To Foreign-Sounding Names Cost Him Delegates.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>EduAnalytics 101</title>
      <link>/2015/07/31/eduanalytics-101/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Jul 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2015/07/31/eduanalytics-101/</guid>
      <description>Preface This is the first in a series of posts that I am putting together in partnership with Edusalsa, an application based at Stanford that seeks to improve how college students explore and choose their courses. Our goal in these posts is to take advantage of the unique data collected from students&amp;rsquo; use of the application in order to learn more about how to model and discuss the accumulation and organization of knowledge within the Stanford community as well as within the larger, global education space.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Geography of Humor</title>
      <link>/2015/05/05/geography-of-humor-the-case-of-the-new-yorker-caption-contest/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 May 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2015/05/05/geography-of-humor-the-case-of-the-new-yorker-caption-contest/</guid>
      <description>Update: Published Article [September 2015] An extenstion of this blog post (using data on submissions and aesthetically improved choropleths!) was published in The New Yorker. See here for the article and here for the relevant R Notebook for replicating the visuals.12
Intro About 10 years ago The New Yorker began a weekly contest. It was not a contest of writing talents in colorful fiction nor of investigative prowess in journalism, instead it was a contest of short and sweet humor.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>