<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Bar charts on The Little Dataset</title>
    <link>/categories/bar-charts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Bar charts on The Little Dataset</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 14 Sep 2017 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/categories/bar-charts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>The United Nations of Words</title>
      <link>/2017/09/14/the-united-nations-of-words/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Sep 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2017/09/14/the-united-nations-of-words/</guid>
      <description>Newsletter e-mails are often artifacts of faded interests or ancient online shopping endeavors. They can be nostalgia-inducing &amp;ndash; virtual time capsules set in motion by your past self at $t-2$, and egged on by your past self at $t-1$. Remember that free comedy show, that desk lamp purchase (the one that looks Pixar-esque), that political campaign&amp;hellip; oof, actually let&amp;rsquo;s scratch that last one. But, without careful care, newsletters breed like rabbits and mercilessly crowd inboxes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The One With All The Quantifiable Friendships, Part 2</title>
      <link>/2017/06/26/the-one-with-all-the-quantifiable-friendships-part-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jun 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2017/06/26/the-one-with-all-the-quantifiable-friendships-part-2/</guid>
      <description>Since finishing my first year of my PhD, I have been spending some quality time with my computer. Sure, the two of us had been together all throughout the academic year, but we weren&amp;rsquo;t doing much together besides pdf-viewing and type-setting. Around spring break, when I discovered you can in fact freeze your computer by having too many exams/section notes/textbooks simultaneously open, I promised my MacBook that over the summer we would try some new things together.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>EduAnalytics 101</title>
      <link>/2015/07/31/eduanalytics-101/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Jul 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2015/07/31/eduanalytics-101/</guid>
      <description>Preface This is the first in a series of posts that I am putting together in partnership with Edusalsa, an application based at Stanford that seeks to improve how college students explore and choose their courses. Our goal in these posts is to take advantage of the unique data collected from students&amp;rsquo; use of the application in order to learn more about how to model and discuss the accumulation and organization of knowledge within the Stanford community as well as within the larger, global education space.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Geography of Humor</title>
      <link>/2015/05/05/geography-of-humor-the-case-of-the-new-yorker-caption-contest/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 May 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2015/05/05/geography-of-humor-the-case-of-the-new-yorker-caption-contest/</guid>
      <description>Update: Published Article [September 2015] An extenstion of this blog post (using data on submissions and aesthetically improved choropleths!) was published in The New Yorker. See here for the article and here for the relevant R Notebook for replicating the visuals.12
Intro About 10 years ago The New Yorker began a weekly contest. It was not a contest of writing talents in colorful fiction nor of investigative prowess in journalism, instead it was a contest of short and sweet humor.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Rise of the New Kind of Cabbie</title>
      <link>/2015/03/30/the-rise-of-the-new-kind-of-cabbie-a-comparison-of-uber-and-taxi-drivers/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Mar 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2015/03/30/the-rise-of-the-new-kind-of-cabbie-a-comparison-of-uber-and-taxi-drivers/</guid>
      <description>Intro One day back in the early 2000&amp;rsquo;s, I commandeered one of my mom&amp;rsquo;s many spiral notebooks. I&amp;rsquo;d carry the notebook all around Manhattan, allowing it to accompany me everywhere from pizza parlors to playgrounds, while the notebook waited eagerly for my parents to hail a taxicab so it could fulfill its eventual purpose. Once in a cab, after clicking my seat belt into place (of course!), I&amp;rsquo;d pull out the notebook in order to develop one of my very first spreadsheets.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>(TGI)Friday the 13th</title>
      <link>/2015/03/11/tgi-friday-the-13th/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Mar 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2015/03/11/tgi-friday-the-13th/</guid>
      <description>Intro I was born on November 13th, 1992. And, while that might be sufficient information to verify my identity to that pre-recorded human on the other end of my calls to the bank, there is an important detail always excluded in this formal expression of one’s birth date: the day of the week. And what makes this seemingly unremarkable fact about me exciting (or disturbing, depending on your take) is that pesky, frequently ignored detail.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The One With All The Quantifiable Friendships</title>
      <link>/2015/01/20/the-one-with-all-the-quantifiable-friendships/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2015/01/20/the-one-with-all-the-quantifiable-friendships/</guid>
      <description>Disclaimer This post does not refer to actual friendships&amp;ndash;no, I am writing about Friends the television show and the corresponding fictional friendships born out of the 1990&amp;rsquo;s sitcom universe.
Intro Given Netflix&amp;rsquo;s much anticipated addition of Friends to their online streaming empire, it is no surprise that public attention has refocused on the show. On a whim that was more nostalgic than anything else, I started re-watching episodes in the &amp;ldquo;sweet spot&amp;rdquo; of its 10-season run (seasons 3 &amp;amp; 4, in my opinion).</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>