<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Model on The Little Dataset</title>
    <link>/tags/model/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Model on The Little Dataset</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 29 Jan 2018 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/tags/model/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Social Networks and the Endurance of Economic Injury</title>
      <link>/2018/01/29/social-networks-and-the-endurance-of-economic-injury/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Jan 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2018/01/29/social-networks-and-the-endurance-of-economic-injury/</guid>
      <description>Killing Two Birds with One Paper My last fall semester exam was for Social Economics class. Reading through packets of model summaries, I set out to determine which model &amp;ndash; besides the obviously lovable Coate and Loury (1993) &amp;ndash; I would most like to understand, remember, and explain. That is, I picked a paper to write about here&amp;hellip; which I could also use in my intellectual battle with those pesky blue books.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Anxious Optimization</title>
      <link>/2016/10/26/anxious-optimization/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2016/10/26/anxious-optimization/</guid>
      <description>On the morning of my dynamic programming midterm, I tried to calm myself by recalling the golden rules of grad school that have been passed down through the generations1:
 grades don&amp;rsquo;t matter&amp;hellip; nothing matters.
 However, I quickly realized that by adopting this perspective I was simply subbing out test anxiety for existential anxiety. And, come to think of it, the latter didn&amp;rsquo;t seem to be helpful, while the former could actually aid in my short-term goals &amp;ndash; namely, jotting down lots of equations into a collection of small blue booklets.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>