<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Phd on The Little Dataset</title>
    <link>/tags/phd/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Phd on The Little Dataset</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 07 Sep 2017 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/tags/phd/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>You Think, Therefore I Am</title>
      <link>/2017/09/07/you-think-there-i-am/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Sep 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2017/09/07/you-think-there-i-am/</guid>
      <description>Intro Hello world, I am now a G2 in economics PhD-land. This means I have moved up in the academic hierarchy; I now reign over my very own cube, and I am taking classes in my fields of interest. For me that means: Social Economics, Behavioral Economics, and Market Design. That also means I am coming across a lot of models, concepts, results that I want to tell you (whoever you are!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Where My Girls At? (In The Sciences)</title>
      <link>/2016/05/24/where-my-girls-at-in-the-sciences/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 May 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2016/05/24/where-my-girls-at-in-the-sciences/</guid>
      <description>Intro In the current educational landscape, there is a constant stream of calls to improve female representation in the sciences. However, the call to action is often framed within the aforementioned nebulous realm of “the sciences”—an umbrella term that ignores the distinct environments across the scientific disciplines. To better understand the true state of women in “the sciences,” we must investigate representation at the discipline level in the context of both undergraduate and doctoral education.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Alex&#39;s Adventures in Academia-land</title>
      <link>/2016/05/08/alex-s-adventures-in-academia-land/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 May 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2016/05/08/alex-s-adventures-in-academia-land/</guid>
      <description>Intro While I usually use this blog to work on casual pet projects, I wanted to take an opportunity to use the medium to discuss academic research. Writing is an instinctive mechanism for me to process my thoughts on a topic, but it is one that I use sparingly to discuss the meta-narrative of my own decisions and behavior. The impetus for this self-reflection is the following exciting news: I’ll be pursuing my PhD in economics at Harvard starting this fall!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>This Post is Brought to You by the National Science Foundation</title>
      <link>/2015/12/31/this-post-is-brought-to-you-by-the-national-science-foundation/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Dec 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2015/12/31/this-post-is-brought-to-you-by-the-national-science-foundation/</guid>
      <description>Intro I have officially finished applying for my PhD. While the application process included many of the same elements that I had previously encountered as a fresh-faced1 17-year-old (think standardized testing without the #2 pencils and lots more button clicking), I am no longer applying as a (relatively) blank slate&amp;ndash;a future liberal arts student who will float and skip between disciplines until being neatly slotted into a major. Instead, we PhD applicants have already zeroed in on a particular area of study&amp;ndash;in my case, economics.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>