<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Stacked area charts on The Little Dataset</title>
    <link>/categories/stacked-area-charts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Stacked area charts on The Little Dataset</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 26 Jun 2017 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/categories/stacked-area-charts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>The One With All The Quantifiable Friendships, Part 2</title>
      <link>/2017/06/26/the-one-with-all-the-quantifiable-friendships-part-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jun 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2017/06/26/the-one-with-all-the-quantifiable-friendships-part-2/</guid>
      <description>Since finishing my first year of my PhD, I have been spending some quality time with my computer. Sure, the two of us had been together all throughout the academic year, but we weren&amp;rsquo;t doing much together besides pdf-viewing and type-setting. Around spring break, when I discovered you can in fact freeze your computer by having too many exams/section notes/textbooks simultaneously open, I promised my MacBook that over the summer we would try some new things together.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>This Post is Brought to You by the National Science Foundation</title>
      <link>/2015/12/31/this-post-is-brought-to-you-by-the-national-science-foundation/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Dec 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2015/12/31/this-post-is-brought-to-you-by-the-national-science-foundation/</guid>
      <description>Intro I have officially finished applying for my PhD. While the application process included many of the same elements that I had previously encountered as a fresh-faced1 17-year-old (think standardized testing without the #2 pencils and lots more button clicking), I am no longer applying as a (relatively) blank slate&amp;ndash;a future liberal arts student who will float and skip between disciplines until being neatly slotted into a major. Instead, we PhD applicants have already zeroed in on a particular area of study&amp;ndash;in my case, economics.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>