<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Open data on The Little Dataset</title>
    <link>/tags/open-data/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Open data on The Little Dataset</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 14 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/tags/open-data/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Dynamics of Pretrial Jail Populations</title>
      <link>/2019/01/14/dynamics-of-pretrial-jail-populations/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2019/01/14/dynamics-of-pretrial-jail-populations/</guid>
      <description>A Daily Census of Pretrial Inmates I&amp;rsquo;ve spent a good amount of time this fall learning about pretrial detention and bail setting practices across the country. While much of the empirical research I&amp;rsquo;ve encountered on pretrial detention uses either aggregated1 or restricted access data, it turns out that there is a granular pretrial detention dataset that frollicks freely on the internet. As of 7/1/16, Connecticut has published &amp;ldquo;a daily census of every inmate held in jail while awaiting trial.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>It&#39;s Raining Cats and Dogs Data</title>
      <link>/2018/10/30/cats-vs-dogs/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Oct 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2018/10/30/cats-vs-dogs/</guid>
      <description>Meow-tivation1 In my day-to-day, I often work with data on ages and names. Age is an important covariate to include in regressions; its continuous evolution can also lend itself to clever regression discontinuity designs.2 Meanwhile, names can be used to infer often omitted demographic variables such as gender and race.3 I have seen these two variables collected for scores and scores of people&amp;hellip; but, what about when the sample isn&amp;rsquo;t people anymore?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Building Visualizations Using City Open Data</title>
      <link>/2016/09/30/building-visualizations-using-city-open-data-philly-school-comparisons/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Sep 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2016/09/30/building-visualizations-using-city-open-data-philly-school-comparisons/</guid>
      <description>Intro There is a collection of notes that accompanies me throughout my day, slipped into the deep pockets of my backpack. The collection consists of small notebooks and post-its featuring sentence fragments written in inky Sharpie or scratched down frantically using some pen that was (of course) dying at the time. Ideas, hypotheses, some jokes. Mostly half baked and sometimes completely raw. Despite this surplus of scribbles, I often struggle when it comes acting on the intention of the words that felt so quick and simple to jot down&amp;hellip; In fact, I often feel myself acting within the confines of this all too perfect graphical representation of project development:</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>